Guide to the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, records
1976-1983
RU 743
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.5
(4 boxes)
The records consist of minutes, reports, memoranda, rosters, agendas, and reviews documenting the activities of the Council on Planning and Priorities and the Executive Committee of the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences.
Yale University. Faculty of Arts and Sciences
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 14-A (YRG 14-A), Records of governing bodies and committees of the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, reports, memoranda, rosters, agendas, and reviews documenting the activities of the Council on Planning and Priorities and the Executive Committee of the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Departments; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Faculty of Arts and Sciences
- Records of the Executive Committee, 1978-1983; Accession 1987-A-089
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2019.
  - Faculty rosters
    - 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting agenda, 1978 September-December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agenda, memos, program proposals, 1979 January-May (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agenda & memos, 1979 September-1981 May (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Agenda, memos, reports, 1980 September-1981 May (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Agenda, report on faculty appointments, 1981 September-October (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Faculty statistics, affirmative action information, 1981 November-December (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Meeting agenda, 1982 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Handbook revisions - Draft, 1982 September-November (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Records of the Council on Planning and Priorities, 1976-1983; Accession 1987-A-090
  - Background materials, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Budget reports, 1977 December-1978 April (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, memos, reports, 1978 October-November (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budget proposals, 1979 January-April (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, memos, reports, 1979 March-November (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Operating budget (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and reports, 1980 January-September (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Minutes and memos, 1980 October-1981 May (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Minutes and memos, 1981 September-1983 April (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1983 April (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Committee reviews, 1983 May-November (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Yale and New Haven (Box 2, Folder 12)